https://btemplates.com/privacy-policy/

Free Blogger Templates BTemplates, the best place for Blogger templates since 2008.
Templates by:
Style
Magazine Gallery Minimalist Elegant Girly Simple Store Neutral Tumblr like
Features
Premium Responsive Adapted from WordPress Ads ready SEO friendly Fast load With slider Drop down menu Footer columns Post thumbnails Social bookmarking
Topics
Anime Music Love Animals Art Books Cars City Culture Gadgets Family Fantasy Fashion Food and Drink Games Home and Decoration Health and Beauty Internet Kids Movies Nature News People Space Science Travel
Columns
1 Column 2 Columns 3 Columns 4 Columns Right sidebar Left sidebar Left and right sidebars
Colors
Black Blue Brown Gray Green Orange Pink Red Violet White Yellow
Search Privacy PolicyWho we areBTemplates.comOur website address is: https://btemplates.com.We are located at: Mexico city, Mexico.Online since 2008.What personal data we collect and why we collect itCommentsWhen visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.CookiesIf you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.If you favorite an item, the item id and name is store in a cookie. This cookie contains no personal data.If you visit our login page, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.Do Not Track (DNT) is an optional browser setting that allows you to express your preferences regarding tracking by advertisers and other third-parties. We DO respond to DNT signals.NewsletterIf you subscribe to our newsletter we save your email address to deliver the newsletter to your inbox.Embedded content from other websitesArticles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.AnalyticsMatomo is used to analyse the behaviour of the website visitors to identify potential pitfalls; not found pages, search engine indexing issues, which contents are the most appreciated… Once the data is processed (number of visitors reaching a not found pages, viewing only one page…), Matomo is generating reports for website owners to take action, for example changing the layout of the pages, publishing some fresh content… etc.Matomo is processing the following data:CookiesUser IDOrder IDLocation of the userAnd also:Date and timeTitle of the page being viewedURL of the page being viewedURL of the page that was viewed prior to the current pageScreen resolutionTime in local timezoneFiles that were clicked and downloadedLink clicks to an outside domainPages generation timeCountry, region, cityMain Language of the browserUser Agent of the browserPaymentsPayments are processed by Paypal. Your use of Paypal is subject to the Paypal privacy policy and terms of use.Who we share your data withThe data gathered by this site is not share with third parties.How long we retain your dataIf you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.What rights you have over your dataIf you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.Where we send your dataVisitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.Contact informationIf you have any inquiry about your data feel free to contact us at:
moc.setalpmetbhello bots@bots are friends not foodofniAdditional informationHow we protect your dataWe maintain technical, physical, and administrative security measures designed to provide reasonable protection for your Personal Data against loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, and alteration. The security measures include firewalls, data encryption, physical access controls at the data centers, and information access authorization controls. While we are dedicated to securing our systems, you are responsible for securing and maintaining the privacy of your password and account/profile registration information and verifying that the personal data we maintain about you is accurate and current.Subscribe by emailReceive the latest templates, news and discounts directly in your inbox. Name Subscription status
×
Terms of use Privacy policy
